skins.cash 2018-09-06

# Privacy Policy | Skins.Cash

_**Last updated: 24.05.2018**_

## SECTION 1. PURPOSE OF THIS POLICY

At Skins.Cash, We are committed to keeping Your information safe and secure. Please read the following Policy so that You understand Your rights in relation to this information, including how Your information will be collected, stored, used and processed.

In providing You with Our Website, We naturally collect information about You. This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") sets out what We collect, how We store, use that information, who We might share it with, and the steps We take to make sure it stays private and secure. 

This Privacy Policy is inalienable part of Skins.Cash Website Terms of Use, available on Our Website. The terms and definitions referred to in this Privacy Policy are specified in the Skins.Cash Website Terms of Use.

Please read the following information carefully to understand Our practices regarding Your information and how We will use it. By continuing to use Our Website, You acknowledge that You have read, understood and accepted the information described in this Privacy Policy. If any User does not agree with this Privacy Policy in general or any part of it, such User should not access or use the Website.

If You agree with this Privacy Policy, You must click on the respective button suggested to You. 

##  SECTION 2. COLLECTION, PROCESSING AND USE OF YOUR INFORMATION 

2.1. Information We collect when You access the Website 

When You visit the Website, We collect the information sent to Us by Your computer, mobile phone, or other access device. This information includes:   

  * Your IP address; 

  * Device information including, but not limited to, identifier, name, and type of operating system; 

  * Mobile network information; 

  * Standard web information, such as Your browser type and the pages You access on Our Website. 

We collect this information in order to:   

  * Administer Our Website, personalize Our Website for You; 

  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activity in connection with Our Website and services and provide third parties with aggregated and anonymized statistical information about Our Users; 

  * Prevent, deter and investigate violation of this Privacy Policy and Our Website of Use, or any fraud and other illegal activities. 

When You access the Website or use Our Service We may place small data files called cookies on Your computer or other device. We use these technologies to recognize You as Our User, customize Our Website for and to monitor usage of Our Website. See Section 3 of this Privacy Policy for more information.

2.2. Information We collect when You use the Website

When You login to the Website through Your Steam account, in addition to the information collected when You access Our Website, We also collect the information, available on Your Steam account, and namely:   

  * Your name; 

  * Your email; 

  * Your Steam unique numeric identifier. 

We collect this information in order to:   

  * Verify Your identity and Your Steam community profile; 

  * Administer our Website and provide services to You; 

  * Access information about Your Steam Account to provide services to You through the Website;

  * Personalize Our Website for You; 

  * Send You technical notices, support, administrative and marketing messages; 

  * Communicate with You about products, services, promotions, events and other news and information We think will be of interest to You. 

We will not share any of Your Steam login credentials with third parties.

2.3. Information We might ask You to provide to perform transactions 

In certain cases We might ask You to provide additional information on Your identity when You want to perform transactions on the Website. We might ask You to provide any or all of the following information and documents for the purpose of Your identity and respective transaction identification:   

  * Your first and last name; 

  * Your date of birth; 

  * Your phone number; 

  * Your social media profile; 

  * Your previous transaction or payment history; 

  * Any other information, including payment information, that may be required for transaction performance; 

  * Copy of Your ID document, containing valid identification information about You; 

  * Copy of You, holding Your ID document.

We collect this information to:   

  * Verify Your identity; 

  * Verify that the transaction is actually performed by You; 

  * Follow international anti-money-laundering and KYC rules and practices; 

  * Prevent any fraud or illegal activities; 

  * Enable the transaction performance; 

  * Follow requirements on person identification, established by Payment processors; 

  * Administer Our Website and provide services to You. 

We may use Your personal data and other information We collect to detect, investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities, develop new products and services and to verify compliance with the Website Terms of Use.

If You do not provide Us with any of the requested personal data, You may not be able to use the Website properly. 

We may refuse You access to Our Service and Website should we, in good faith, have doubts as to validity or authenticity of any personal data You provide.

2.4. Location Data

When You use a location-enabled device to access Our Website and services, we may collect geographical location data or use various means to determine the location, such as sensor data from Your device that may, for instance, provide data on nearby cell towers and Wi-Fi access spots. 

2.5. Notice to parents. 

We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 13. Skins.Cash encourages parents to instruct their children to never give out personal information when online. Parents who are concerned about the transfer of personal information from their children may contact Us by email as specified in "Contact" section of this Privacy Policy.

##  SECTION 3. COOKIES 

We use cookies and other similar technologies (e.g. web beacons, Flash cookies, etc.) ("Cookies") to enhance Your experience using the Website. Cookies are small text files that are placed on Your computer by websites that You visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, and to deliver a better and more personalized service.

Cookies may be either "persistent" Cookies or "session" Cookies. A persistent cookie consists of a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, which will be stored by the browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date (unless deleted by the user before the expiry date). A session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. 

We use the following Cookies:   

  * Strictly necessary Cookies. These are Cookies that are required for the operation of the Website. 

  * Analytical/performance Cookies. They allow Us to recognize and count the number of Users and to see how Users move around the Website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way the Website works. We use Google Analytics which is a web analytics tool that helps Us understand how Users engage with the Website. Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track User interactions as in Our case, where they are used to collect information about how Users use Our Website and how they use it. This information is used to compile reports and to help Us improve Our Website. The reports disclose Website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how You visit Our Website – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites You use, visit this Google [ page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

  * Functionality Cookies. These are used to recognize You when You return to the Website. This enables Us to personalize Our content for You (for example, Your choice of language). 

You can find more information about Cookies and how to manage them at <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>. You may control the use of Cookies within Your internet browsers’ settings. If you reject or delete certain Cookies, be aware that the performance of the related features and functions of Our Website and services may be impaired. 

##  SECTION 4. HOW WE MIGHT SHARE YOUR PERSONAL DATA 

4.1 We may share Your personal data where:   

  * We need to in order to operate Our Website and Service. 

  * We need in order to perform Your transactions on the Website through or partner Payment processors. 

  * We have a public or legal duty to do so (e.g. to assist with detecting fraud, tax evasion, financial crime prevention, regulatory reporting, litigation or defending legal rights and property, including Our own). 

  * We have asked for Your permission to share Your information and You have agreed. 

4.2 We may share Your personal data and information with:   

  * Companies that We plan to merge with or be acquired by (should such a combination occur, We will notify You and will require that the newly combined entity follow these terms with respect to Your personal data); 

  * Law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties when We are compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order, or similar legal procedure; or We believe in good faith that the disclosure of personal data is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity or to investigate violations of any of Our policies; 

  * Our vendors and agents including hosting providers, hired by Us to provide services, game developers; 

  * Payment processors (for the purpose of Your transactions performance when using the Website). 

4.3 What We will not use Your personal data for:   

  * We will not provide Your personal data to any other Website users or third parties other than described in this Privacy Policy without notifying You first. 

  * We will not sell or rent Your personal data to third parties, other than as described in this Privacy Policy without notifying You first. 

4.4 Links to Third Party Websites or Services, and Third Party services:   

  * Our Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of Our partner networks, game developers, advertisers, Payment processors, etc.. 

  * If You follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites and any services that may be accessible through them have their own privacy policies and that We do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies or for any information, including personal data that may be collected through these websites or services, such as contact and location data. Please check these policies before You submit any information or personal data to these websites or use these services. 

  * Our Website may also contain services of/from Our partners, vendors, game developers. 

  * In order to provide Services to You and/or for the purpose of duly transactions performance on the Website, when You use Our Website, it, may, from time to time, get and/or collect User’s personal data, such as Your name (username, login) and/or other identifiers from Our partners’, vendors’, game developers’ Services. We will not provide this data to any other Website users or third parties other than described in this Privacy Policy without notifying You first. Please note that these services that Our Website may contain have their own privacy policies and that We do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies or for any information, including personal data that may be collected through these services, such as contact and location data. Please check policies of such services before using these services. 

  * For the purpose of duly transactions performance on the Website Users might be required to provide their personal and payment processing data (such as name, surname, address, copies of ID cards or other identifying documents, residence place confirmation documents, credit card identification data) to the respective Payment processor, including the consent for processing these data by the payment services in order to carry out the requested transactions. Please note that the respective personal and payment processing data provided by You to a third party Payment processor shall be collected, stored and processed solely by the respective Payment processor and not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should read carefully and follow the applicable privacy policies of the Payment processor. 

##  SECTION 5. HOW WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE

We protect Your information using security standards such as firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls to Our premises and information access authorization controls. We also authorize access to Your information only for those employees or contractors who require it to fulfill their job or service responsibilities.

Please note that transmission of data or information (including communications by e-mail) over the internet or other publicly accessible networks is not one hundred percent secure. Please note that We are not liable for the security of any data You are transmitting over the internet. 

##  SECTION 6. HOW WE TRANSFER YOUR INFORMATION 

We store and process Your information using cloud services in various jurisdictions, including the United States of America. As such, the information that We collect from You may be transferred to, and stored in various jurisdictions outside of Your country of residence and outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). The laws on processing such information, including where such information is classed as "personal data", in these locations may be less stringent than in Your country. It may also be processed by staff operating outside of Your country or the EEA who work for us, for one of Our service providers or one of our business partners. By submitting Your information, You agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that Your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## SECTION 7. YOUR RIGHTS

You may access, review and edit Your personal data at any time by contacting Our support team. You may be requested by Our team to provide the respective confirmation documents in case of Your personal data information change. 

European users have the right under applicable privacy laws to ask Us to provide details of the personal data We hold about them or in certain circumstances may request We delete their personal data. 

To exercise the abovementioned rights, please contact Us by email as specified in "Contact" section of this Privacy Policy. 

A request on access, review, provision of details, amendment or deletion of personal data is usually processed within 72 hours from the moment We receive it. However, due to technical reasons delays are possible, and in such case We shall process the respective request within a reasonable term. 

##  SECTION 8. UPDATES OR AMENDMENTS TO THIS POLICY

We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at Our discretion. Any changes can be viewed in the "Last Updated" field above, so please check the section regularly. 

If We make any material changes, We will post the new policy on the Website, with a new effective date. 

##  SECTION 9. CONTACT

Intellectual property notification: This document belongs to the Website Owner and is protected by copyright laws. It’s copying and/or use by any third party in full or in part without prior written consent of the Website Owner is strictly prohibited. If You have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy or want to exercise any of Your rights as specified herein, please feel free to contact Us through Live Chat or by email at [ info@skins.cash](mailto:info@skins.cash)
